<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OUFC Website</title>
    <link>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/</link>
    <description>Recent content on OUFC Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/top/about/</guid>
      <description>The Oxford University Fencing Club is one of the oldest surviving fencing clubs in the country, certainly one of the oldest outside of London. Throughout its history, it has played an important role in British fencing, and its history reflects that of the sport in general in England. The club was founded in 1891, placing it at the forefront of the revival of fencing as a sport in Great Britain which really began in the 1890’s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>President&#39;s welcome</title>
      <link>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/presidents-welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/presidents-welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Oxford University Fencing Club website!
Founded in 1891, OUFC is one of Britain’s oldest and most successful fencing clubs. The club caters for all levels, from beginners to international.
Foil, epee and sabre training are all on offer at the club. Advanced and intermediate fencers receive expert tuition from our club coach, Tomek Walicki, who leads a weekly training session and offers individual lessons throughout the week. In addition there are two club nights every week with a mixture of coached, structured and free fencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/about_me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/about_me/</guid>
      <description>asdasdasdads sdf sdf sdf sdf sfd sdfsdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>zxczxczxczxczxczxc zxczxczxc zxczxczxczxcizxczxczxcasd aasd asdasd asdadsc xcvfvjh</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/top/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/top/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/top/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pawelsawicz.github.io/oufc-website/top/support/</guid>
      <description>The rising costs of coaching, equipment, and generally the increasing cost of student life in Oxford does take a heavy toll on the extent to which our members can fence. In order to offer our members the opportunity to pursue their goals in fencing, we would like to subsidise as much as possible all activities that will enable our fencers to attain that high level of achievement which OUFC has been proud of since 1891.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>